I'll always be watching you from your shadows.
Hello?
Evening! It's your favorite florist!
What do you want, Colonel?!
Sorry about that.
I was a bit drunk and ended up buying a lot of flowers.
I'd be grateful if you'd be willing to take a few off my hands.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Are you sure?
Yes, it's nothing.
I'll have to kindly refuse the flowers.
I don't own a vase to put them in.
But thank you for giving me a call. Good night.
Why does he have such good timing when it comes to things like these?
Can't focus. My body is still puzzled about what to do.
Shuuchuu dekitenaina mada karada ga mayotteirunda
I'm trembling. I can't stop even if I try to control myself.
Furueteitanja kontoroorushitatte burerunda
Although neither sun nor moon are on my side,
Taiyou mo tsuki mo nanmo kanzen ni kocchi muiteinaiga
"I've no choice but to try,"
Yarushikanainda
Those were the words I muttered to myself.
Iikikaseruyouni sotto tsubuyaita
The odds aren't on my side, but running way'd be gutless.
Joukyou wa waruiga tada nigedasunja konjou nainaa
Even if I can't see the future, I'll just have to win it over with courage.
Tenbou wa naiga dokyou de kuria suru shika naiya
Need to keep distance from the target as I hold myself back.
Shoudou wa osaetamama taagetto to no kankaku sagure
All that's needed for victory is pride to win.
Hitsuyou na mon wa katsu puraido
Will we celebrate with the wine of victory
Ajiwau nowa shouri no bishu ka
Or'll we end up kissing their feet in defeat?
Soretomo haiboku no kujuu ka
There are two outcomes to everything.
Sou subete wa futatsu ni hitotsu
I want to control destiny.
Ayatsuritai unmei no ito
I need to seize the golden opportunity with my hands.
Zekkou no goorudentaimu kono te de tsukame
I'll finish it up with my best poker face,
Konshin no pookaafeisu kimete shikakeruyo
And drag them into a world of illusions.
Iryuujon no sekai e hikizurikonde
I'll find my way out of this endless pressure game,
Saigennai puresshaageemu sururito nukete
And leap over the borderline of honor.
Eikou no boodaarain tobikoeru tameni
How many? What'll I need to sacrifice to make it happen?
Haumenii? Dorekurai no daishou ga iru?
What is the one thing I don't want to let go?
Tebanashitakunai mon wa dore?
A man thought to be Scar was sighted on a mountain trail near the area.
We should start here.
An abandoned mine?
That's right.
This town, Baschool, is now a ghost town.
It would make a great hideout.
How troublesome.
So we're going to split up.
If a party spots him, report back immediately.
Roger!
We'll accompany the Elric Brothers.
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder if they're coming to keep an eye on us.
Most likely.
Conflict at Baschool
Now...
How should we get rid of these two...
Hey! I just saw a shadow!
What?!
Over here!
Hey! Hang on!
Hey! Wait!
They disappeared!
Where did they go?!
Did they go into that room?!
Damn them, running around!
We were able to get rid of them, but...
...this place...
...is a bit...
...too big, don't you think?!
Where are Scar and that little girl?
If they don't randomly show up,
it'll be impossible for us to find them...
Sir Alphonse!
Sir Alphonse!!!
Hey!
No way...
Sir Alphonse!
She really showed up...
What are you doing here?!
May!
Great! I found you!
Don't tell me... you came here looking for me?
Yeah! I wanted to see you!
Sir Al...
I wanted to see you and learn more about Eastern Alchemy...
Oh my gosh! Am I dreaming? Sir Al came looking for me?
Huh?
Hey, brat!
I've been dying to see you!
I'm not letting you get away this time!
Hurry up and teach us Eastern Alchemy!
You brothers are feuding for my hand!
But you're not my type, Edward!
Don't play dumb with me!
Hey, Al...
Oh, sorry about that.
Ow...
I hit my head.
Who is that woman, Sir Alphonse?!
How horrible... You have me, and yet...
No! She's just an old friend of mine!
Wait... Why am I talking like a two-timer?
May, please don't run off by yourself-
The Elric Brothers?!
Who are you?
It's me, Marcoh.
Dr. Marcoh?!
What happened to your face?
What are you doing here?
The Elric Brothers!
Who the heck are you?
Don't you dare say you forgot!
I'm Yoki, the great coal-mine owner of Youswell!
Guess I forgot.
Actually, I don't even think I know you.
How awful! After all those things you did to me...
Youswell
Youswell, a mining town.
I, Yoki, was a soldier and manager of the town.
The people of the town lived happily due to my efforts.
Hurry up and pay
your taxes!
We can't because you keep cutting our salaries!
And that's where the uttermost villain,
Edward Elric, a State Alchemist, showed up!
Silver pocketwatch!?
State Alchemist!!
Gold!!
I want to buy the rights to the coal mine with this
But it was a trap!
What is this about, Mr. Alchemist?!
All the gold I received from you turned into rocks!
They were working together!
And I, who had the mine stolen from me...
...suffered at the hands of the people who forgot what they owed me...
...and was given a bad name by the military.
I started many businesses in order to return to popularity...
...but it all ended in failure...
My investments...
...also ended in failure...
And my last resort...
...was to ask a millionaire for a goodwill loan...
If only...
If only it hadn't been for those Elric Brothers...
And that was when I swore...
Swore to take revenge against those two who brought me down like this.
An act of revenge far worse than death!
I won't lose to a thief like you!
No... I'm not really a thief...
I'm telling you, there's nothing between us!
Who cares! I need to ask you about Eastern Alchemy!
Hey! How about you two listen to me?!
Yeah, whatever. It must have been hard, old man.
I totally understand how you feel.
Quit pretending like you were listening!
You can't find Miss Winry?
Seriously... what were you all doing?
We're terribly sorry...
I'll go look for her.
Two men from Charlie squad come with me.
Yes, sir!
Major Miles.
I know. Scar, right?
I'll contact you if I find him.
This place is no good either, huh?
There's barely anything here.
You're Scar, right?
Sir Kimblee would like to see you.
Come with us.
I'm surprised you were able to find me.
But do you really think the two of you can take me?
Probably not, if we were ordinary humans.
If  we were ordinary humans, that is!
Chimeras, huh...
Interesting!
I've learned a lot since then.
First, the method to create a philosopher's stone.
Second, the history of this country. And that there's something odd about the alchemy this country uses.
That's why we came after this girl, seeking a possibility in Eastern Alchemy from Xing.
Nothing less to be expected from you.
The thing is, someone realized it far before you did.
These are the research documents he left us.
We think these documents may hold a clue to solving the mystery.
So if we could decipher it...
Yes, possibly...
But to do that, we need Scar's help.
Why him?!
What was that sound?
That's where Scar went!
Could it be the army?!
You four hide here.
We'll go see what's going on.
Scar is...
He's fat, but that doesn't slow him down at all!
I heard you're powerless unless you can actually touch us.
So we're going to be attacking from a distance.
And we're also aware that you attempt to destroy the ground when things get bad for you.
We'll beat you to a pulp and hand you over to Sir Kimblee!
Talk about good timing.
The Elric Brothers?
This voice...
Brother, they're Kimblee's men from Central.
What?
I get it...
You don't need to do anything besides watch.
We're going to capture Scar-
A monster!!!
W-What was that for?! We're on your sid-
I don't recall having any monsters on our side!
How frightening!
They're going to pretend they're on our side, then eat us!
The fat one back there has a really big mouth! He'll eat me whole!
You brat! Stay put!
Is he faster than Scar?!
Brother?
What's so funny?!
So light!
It feels like my limbs are made of feathers!
Northern automails are fabulous!
Don't get too cocky now...
Huh? I guess my punches lost some force, too.
My spit won't come off that easily!
This is slob?! That's just gross!
In that case...
If I decompose it, it's pretty much water!
Th-That's cold!!
Take this!
What the heck was that for, Brother?!
O-O-Ow! Stop moving!
You're going to tear my skin off!
How did you like my "Touching Cold Metal With Wet Hands and Getting Stuck Together" attack?
Quit getting in our way, Fullmetal Alchemist!
Aren't you on our  side?!
Shut up, pig! I don't know anyone who looks like you!
Besides, anyone can tell you're a bad guy!
If you still insist that you're on our side, prove it!
Fine! I'll transform back, just watch!
I've been waiting for this!
Zampano!
How foolish of you to sheath
your sword in front of your enemy.
Dammit! Get off me!
Okay, I'm going to need you to take a little nap.
He's in fighting shape, now...
Hurry up and get caught already.
Face trial, Scar!
I'll destroy whoever gets in my way.
He's coming head-on, without thinking?
Your steel arm is mine!
Sorry. It's not made out of steel anymore!
Stay still!
Stop it!
Idiot! Why did you come?!
Stay back.
Major Miles.
Wh-What's up with these two?
The people at Central seem to be conducting awful experiments.
Tie them to that pillar over there.
Aye, sir!
Now, Scar...
It doesn't please me to pass judgment on a fellow countryman, but I can't let someone like you run free.
Fellow countryman?
Elric Brothers, we'll take care of the rest...
Winry!
Idiot! Stay away from him!
Let me go... I'll be fine.
How will you be fine?!
Stay away from him, Miss.
Please let me talk to him.
I want to talk to him face to face.
Why did you kill my parents?
No matter what I say, it'll be only be an excuse.
The fact is I killed the Rockbells.
What was that?!
It's in the location of the building we received a report from!
This isn't good. We've been down here for more than twenty-four hours, which is what we promised.
It's the Ice Queen we're talking about.
I'm sure she really sealed the exit.
It's only natural we took so long.
We groped our way here with the lanterns out, after all.
Since they insisted a monster would come if we kept the lights on.
Welcome back.
Thank goodness!
Take these two to the infirmary. Quickly!
Sorry for the trouble...
You have nothing to apologize for.
I thought I told you to seal the exit after twenty-four hours?
Ah. But, look.
It hasn't been twenty-four hours yet.
By the way, Major General Armstrong told me to go by this watch.
General!
Was the advance unit safe?
Just two of them.
I see.
What are you doing here, if I may ask?
I was looking at the mountains.
Winter is nice here, isn't it?
I only see black and white.
It's very plain, and I like it.
Do you think so?
If you look up, there's also the color blue.
It's just like a person's heart, isn't it?
I greatly appreciate you giving us leeway this time, ma'am.
Huh? I have no idea what you're talking about.
Looks like we've got some guests.
It's been a while.
Sorry for asking this the moment of my arrival,
but is there something you owe us an explanation for?
Don't get too close!
All men, stay back!
Dammit!
Fullmetal Alchemist?
Kimblee!
Why the hell didn't you keep an eye on Winry?!
Mr. Kimblee, the roof!
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
We used to talk all night until the sun rose,
Asahi ga noboru made katariattane
And held hands till the sun went under the horizon.
Yuuhi ga shizumu made tsunaida te
Let's walk together like this forever, like light and shadow.
Kouyatte asu mo asatte mo tomo ni ayumou hikari to kage
I stand in the city, staring off into space with lonely eyes.
Samishige ni mitsumeru machi no naka de
I can't find warmth on my own.
Nukumori wa hitori ja mitsukaranakute
By meeting you, I realized
Ai ga konnani tsuyosa ni narukoto
How much strength love could give me.
Shittanda kimi ni deaete hajimete
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
I can't sleep by myself, 'cause I can't dream without you.
Hitori ja nemurenai yume wa mirenaikara
So take me to a place where uncertainty can't reach us
Donna fuan mo todokanai tokoro e
And let us bring light to the night sky with no stars.
Hoshi no yoru mo terashitsuzukeyou
So long as you're with me, I can go to world's end.
Doko made mo yukeru kimi to nara
Even if it's a path I can't walk on my own,
Hitori ja arukenai michi mo futari nara
If you're by my side, I can walk it while humming a tune.
Hanauta utainagara arukerunda
If we're together, the world is mine.
Kimi ga ireba shiawase
Even if an encounter is accompanied by grief,
there is still meaning in it.
The path to take is inscribed in feelings that come and go.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Daydream
Episode 39, Daydream.
Is everything part of a plan devised by a superior being?